signal late night, could we buddy want a piece of me with knives?
And if I learn how the crowd consumes, how applause can become your tomb,
so I built watched fake kings rehearse their magic.
Let me just tell you a little story. Let me just tell you a little story about Alexander Mayer,
who's the fucking cunt. Let me just tell you a little story about this bitch.
She calls me. She says,
I have a big favor to ask you.
You know, I want to have a baby.
You know, it's my dream to have a child.
She's like, would you consider being a donor for my child?
And I told, I'm stupid.
Me, I said I would.
You know, I said I would.
But yes, and then she's like, on the next call,
she said, well, you're gonna be,
you're gonna fuck me for it, right?
You're gonna have sex with me, right?
Alex, I'm just telling 100% truth
and I'm told people about this behind the scenes
and they know exactly what I said
Okay, bitch
You asked for it. You asked where you're gonna get it Alex. You're gonna get it
You asked for my come you wanted if you want to meet me the father of your child both it
Oh, it would be really good. Oh, they're nice to be perfect because you're white, right bitch
It's amazing
Alex the ender mayors asked for my sperm, okay? I swear my fucking father's grave. She did okay
I don't fucking fuck around my dad. She asked for it
Hey, Mason, how are you?
So I got once at Natalie's, but she was acting all weird and stuff like that.
Yeah, I know Natalie's a little bit psycho, but you know what?
I've got my own shit to deal with right now.
I'd say I can't, I can't talk to Natalie, but you know, I know, I know.
She's a little bit, she's a weirdo.
I mean, it's like, but what's going on with you?
Yeah, it was fun.
Yeah, yeah, it's like what would Natalie be like that?
She's a bit back here because I like you know, I played it some I don't know
She's been back here, but I'm trying to tell about how it's other mayors asking for my sperm right now
You know she asked for my sperm to my child. You know that and now she's denying it. I have proof
I approve not it. I didn't know about that stuff
Yeah, she asked me and she said she wanted me to fuck her and that's how I was gonna give it to her, okay?
That's how that's what she said to me on the phone. Yeah, but it's like I thought I was your friend and stuff like that
You are you are but you can't have a child Mason and I mean it's not with me at least but you know
I mean, I'm gonna tell you the truth. It's not about you Mason
I'm trying to tell a different story, but let's go to you. How are you do Mason?
But yeah, it's like you're frozen
Oh my gosh, Roseanne.
Oh, she's such a fucking liar.
Oh, I can't talk to Psyche for legal reasons.
Why? Because you're fucking threatening my life?
Hey, you're talking to my family, you fucking bitch!
How about that?
Alexander Mears!
Okay? You're threatening my fucking family!
Give my fucking address out!
Fuck your mother! My father!
You're a fucking bitch!
Sorry, Mason.
What do you think of that, Alex?
You're denying it?
You're a fucking lunatic!
Oh my god the fucking bitch
I'm at an avenue bitch
Stop lying
You're the friend of my life
I'm gonna play all the clips
You can't be your reason
I'm gonna play the clips
I'm gonna play the clips you're the friend of my life
You can't be your right now
I'll play the clips
You're the friend of my life bitch
Show me where I'm from in your life
Show me where I'm done to your family bitch
Show me
How about that?
You're fucking cunt
You're the fucking worst bitch I've ever met in my life
Oh you're disgusting
You've greased, cheeky, and you're cunt
You're fuckin' at me in the SDDs!
Go to QB Farms, look at Alexander Mayer's, this fuckin' bitch!
But I've always worked.
Part of the reason that I went into the adult entertainment industry was because I didn't
want to be reliant upon my parents, okay?
Um, judge me however it is that you want to.
I'm not ashamed.
Let's judge you on this, Alex. Let's go to QE Farms and listen to what they have to say about you.
How about that? How about that, Alex? You ready for this, bitch? You ready?
I'm going to QE Farms right now. Let's do what they have to say about it. Okay. QE Farms.
You're pushing this far, bitch. You're pushing this far. I'm going to show everything.
I'm gonna show everything when we read the whole thread.
We're gonna read Q-Farms right now, Alexander Mayer's.
Monica, let's read about you, bitch!
Oh, we're gonna read about you. Let's read everything.
I'm gonna read the whole entire thread, bitch.
You ready?
Okay, I have to go under low-cows because you are a big fucking low-cow.
I'm gonna search Alexander Mayer's and we're gonna share this whole thing.
Let's see what it has to say about you, bitch.
Monica Foster, Alexander Mayer's.
Let's read the whole thing
You want to hear it?
Let's hear it. Let's hear it. You want to share everything about me?
You're gonna share my mom's information. You want to share everything bitch?
We're gonna read the whole QE farms article about you. Let's do it right now
Alexandra Mayers! Monica Foster! There she is! Monica Foster! Alexandra Melody Mayers is a retired porn actress and one of the many people whom Donnie Long has a raging hate-boner for.
Much like other many people in the porn industry, Monica's a raving loon herself!
According to her page on porn and WikiLeaks, she's failed at just about every aspect of her life.
Considering the source of information, it's been hard to separate fact from fiction.
But I'll provide a rundown anyway.
Monica was born in Washington, say to a mother who was a teacher, a father who was an engineer.
According to the Wiki, Monica's father came out of the closet as gay in 93, then ran off.
Also, according to the Wiki, Monica was given everything she needed to succeed in life and still failed!
She dropped out of high school, got her GED,
then went into college at Florida Atlantic University.
After one year, she dropped out and became a stripper.
She did that for a few months of her quitting
because she thought she was better than she was.
She then went into porn before retiring
after about 35 scenes.
That's an incredibly short career, by the way.
On average, porn stars usually do at least
a couple hundred scenes throughout their careers.
And you're gonna fail porn star.
Monica has made multiple death threats and has even expressed an desire to have Donnie
Long and others killed by Nazis or the KKK.
Oh, here's your death and suicide threats.
Let's have a look.
Okay, let's have a look. Okay, it's not coming up. Oh, here we are. Oh, I do plan to kill you
Whatever it's created maintains an old house site whether you whether I kill you or just most or just love
Most or just you it will happen or I kill what you love most or just you will happen
Monica is that enough that Kevin Blatt or shy level hook you up with a rapist is that Monica Foster tonight?
Monica Thorn you want a 3rd HIV just enter poor that you the condom
Take it a step further.
Those you know that point, losers.
What, really, what you're dealing with in the devil?
The sooner, the better.
I already had to make condoms mandatory and poor
because you are a sick disease bitch.
Could someone from the KKH or Nazi camp please knock off both Mike Stack,
Sione, Fatty, or Ryder.
If you have anything to do with it, I'll kill you personally, and I'll trust you.
She's a dense red person.
She's an alcoholic.
She's usually seen drinking during her camp shows.
Her wiki page mentions one frequency in particular,
when she's appeared to be drinking excessive amount of red wine.
She looked like she was
Appeared to be making crazy violent movements. It looked haggard at one point of the show
It looks as if she's attempting to eat a house plant
Viewers who are live broadcasts all the respondents to foster making strange comments here's some of the comments
She says she is the largest black people porn star out there today. Tori black is not fresh anymore
Doug T real doesn't help the sisters. She's the most well-connected user out sister out there with websites and cam shows
She's too good-looking. Bill Clinton is a black man drinking alone as foster does constantly. It's one of those warnings that the alcoholism
as Donnie Long as a Reggie hate-boner for her.
Okay, anyway, let's go into more into it.
Oh, do you wanna eat your father,
then you're supposed to take pictures of my father,
you fucking cunt, you're gonna see his fucking cunt whore?
You're gonna put a picture of my father up?
You fucking cunt, I hate you.
I fucking hate you if you die.
You're a fucking the worst bitch I've ever met in my life.
Die, die, you fucking cunt whore.
You're done, bye.
Fucking die in a ditch! You fucking disease! You have this green stuff coming out of your pussy!
Everyone's died! You're literally chasing out the porn industry for this! You fucking bitch!
Clip this now! For I don't need it!
I'm gonna tell the truth about this bitch! I will tell the truth about this fucking bitch!
And he has where I come! As you would have my baby!
Oh, I didn't ask him! Yes you did! He said he wanted me to fuck you too, you fucking bitch! Die!